Burton and Taylor is a drama, tv movie film directed by Richard Laxton.
Legendary acting duo and married couple Richard Burton and Elizabeth Taylor
prepare for a 1983 theatrical production of the play "Private Lives."
Richard Burton, played by Dominic West.
Elizabeth Taylor, played by Helena Bonham Carter.
Kathryn Walker, played by Sarah Hadland.
Chen Sam, played by Lenora Crichlow.
Milton Katselas, played by Stanley Townsend.
Liza Todd Burton, played by Lucille Sharp.
Burton & Taylor is a BBC Four TV film written by William Ivory and directed by Richard Laxton, starring Helena Bonham Carter and Dominic West as legendary acting
duo and former couple, Elizabeth Taylor and Richard Burton during their preparation for a 1983 theatrical production of the play, Private Lives.
The tone is emotional.